# **Sharon Abramovich**

# **Full Stack Developer**

Petach Tikva | 050-9410940 | <u>abra.sharon@gmail.com</u> <u>github.com/SharonAbra</u> | <u>linkedin.com/in/sharonabramovich/</u> | <u>Portfolio</u>

#### **SUMMARY**

Full Stack Developer experienced in JavaScript based programming with a passion for building practical, beautiful and well-performing applications. Enjoys the process of planning, creating and finding elegant solutions. Has strong skills in problem solving, visual thinking and teamwork. Sociable, organized, and drives for the best results.

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Programming Languages: JavaScript (ES6)

Front-End: React.js, Redux, Bootstrap, HTML5, CSS3 Back-End: PostgreSQL, JSON Web Token, Node.js

Software: Git, Github

Development Practices: REST API design, Agile, Web App Architecture (MVC)

#### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

Developers Institute Hackathon - 1st place recipient.

### **TECHNICAL PROJECTS**

### Memory Game - Github | Demo

A full stack educational multiplayer game to enrich English vocabularies.

- Designed a beautiful and clean user interface with React.js, including state management with Redux.
- Developed an efficient node is server to handle data fetching and socket connections.
- Implemented a PostgreSQL database as the basis for the game's vocabulary.

### BuddyBot - Github | Demo

A full stack chatbot app for entertainment and conversation.

- Created an extensive database of triggers and responses using PostgreSQL.
- Developed a node.js server to handle inputs and filter responses.
- Incorporated media from various public APIs to enrich the app and enhance interactivity.

### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Program Director - International MA program**

Tel Aviv, Israel 2013 - 2021

Tel Aviv University

- Implemented a formal education program by forecasting requirements, and verified its success.
- Devised corrective actions to course modules to ensure a quality experience for customers.
- Produced events and activities alongside a team of coordinators and responded to issues in real-time.

## **Administrative Director**

Tel Aviv, Israel

**IES Medical** 

2010-2011

- Managed the foreign residents department and verified that policies are issued quickly and accurately.
- Facilitated efficient customer support services to achieve maximum client satisfaction.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### Full Stack Web Development, JavaScript program

Developers Institute, TLV Coding Bootcamp

Tel Aviv, Israel 06/2021 -12/2021

## BA: Double Major - Psychology and Philosophy

Tel Aviv University

Tel Aviv, Israel 2010 - 2013

#### **LANGUAGES**

Hebrew - native speaker, English - fluent